You
Hey, what gives we don't understand what you're trying to tell us
Who was that I'm gonna try calling back
Is our phone off what's going on
She's not answering at home should we call the cops
Right I'm on my way
I'll take care of things only captain Shao will understand. We need to handle this with care. I
Have a feeling that article is the reason for whatever's happening
Are you saying that this is my fault?
Don't get ahead of yourself
We need to make sure that our friend is safe first
I'll go you stay here with her keep the studio locked and don't leave until I'm back. Okay, I'll make it fast
You sure you don't want help
I
Chung show shows upset. He needs to settle down. We shouldn't let him talk to the cops
There's a chance. He might say something. He shouldn't also
You should be in charge of his phone in the meantime
Got it
It didn't take too long to realize something has changed in the back of my mind your eyes
There ain't nowhere left to hide behind
Time no longer flew like it was when the flash froze everything before without you
I don't know if I could take this road
Every minute that I die back in time
Every single existence rewinds
Something secretive hidden inside your eyes
All mine
All the hobbies and the smiles never faded
I know you'll be by my side when we make it
Come back from the time
Back in time
Die back in time
arbitrage
ppenit
o
The suspect's aggression may stem from an antisocial personality disorder.
He seems to kill at random with no clear motive, but he's a careful planner.
Several cases were initially thought to be suicides, with one important exception.
Wu Lihua was seen getting into a car with this person shortly before her death.
After much deliberation this morning, the department heads decided to release this photo online
to see if a member of the public could help us identify the man.
In just a few short hours, we received multiple tips.
And most of them ID the same person as our suspect.
Liu Min, male, 27, currently working as the executive director of a tech company.
Bet it's a family thing. He was handed the job.
The workers probably hate him too.
Without solid evidence, this is mere speculation.
So keep investigating.
There's someone here to see you.
Where the hell have you been, idiot?
First you leave, and now you're interrupting—
Uh, I got a message right before the meeting.
And then I had to pick the caller up.
Here he is.
You have to calm down.
Liu's gonna handle this.
Plus, Xiao seems reliable.
I'm sure he'll sort things out.
Wait.
Maybe.
There's some info online.
What's your deal?
I'm limiting your internet access, so crazy rumors don't give you more anxiety.
You'll thank me later.
Guess I'll go rest.
Call me when he's back.
I thought you couldn't help us.
What's with the change of heart?
Show me the screenshot taken from the surveillance camera.
Our friend might be in danger.
Oh?
Think they're involved?
Long story.
A man made a strange call using her number.
We've been unable to reach her since.
I see.
And you think it's our killer?
Hard to say.
But the faster we capture him, the sooner we'll get an answer.
Here.
I've got his license plate number.
BS-30X-7948.
I'll go run it.
How is this possible?
So, you find anything else I should know about?
Hey, who else has seen this?
It was posted online this morning, so everybody...
That idiot!
Hey!
Where are you going?
What about your friend who's in trouble?
Something happened in here?
I don't know.
These kids are so damn mysterious.
If it weren't for Liang's case, I wouldn't believe them.
Well, sir, get this.
That plate number's legit.
Care to guess?
Don't be coy.
Speak.
It belongs to Liu Min.
No.
I confiscated his phone.
He should be napping upstairs.
You gotta tell me what's going on?
What?
Wait, where did he go?
Our abilities complement each other.
You can enter the time of a photo, but there's only one way in.
A high five.
You sure there's no other way?
Really?
Afraid not.
This is it.
What if I slap my hand instead?
Would that work, or...?
That's not a good idea.
Think.
You need a guide.
Don't dive solo.
Huh?
Wait.
How did I end up here as myself?
You have the usual 12 hours in the past.
Be smart.
Keep a low profile.
Like you were never there.
I'm only going to observe the murder and look for clues.
I won't attract attention.
I'll be like a shadow.
Then I'll jump out unscathed.
Yo, Liu.
You there?
I guess it really is just me.
Damn.
Where'd he go?
Looks like I'm in a blind spot.
I'll wait here for him to come back.
And then...
Where's my phone?
I'm limiting your internet access so crazy rumors don't give you more anxiety.
You'll thank me later.
Worst timing.
What do I do?
I do...
Yes?
Ma'am, I have a couple of questions for Liu Min.
Mr. Liu, the police are asking for your son!
The nerve of you people! We've been harassed non-stop today!
The surveillance footage you posted on your site is ruining my kid's life!
I'll be frank. We've received a lot of accusations about your son.
We're here to find out the truth. Where is he?
Morons! You believe slanderous comments made online by jealous trolls?
I should sue you! He's being cyber-bullied!
How could my son be involved in serial murders? It's ridiculous!
People point to him because they hate our company and wealth! It's petty revenge!
I'm so sorry. I don't mean to trouble you.
No, Big. What's on the way?
It's been such a weird day, and Kebs were ignoring me.
At least your parents won't have to wait now.
Please, sir! Let me do my job! This can't be completely unfounded!
Listen, it'd be easier if we could just talk to him, briefly.
Not a chance! He's gone through more than enough already aside from this.
Don't make his life any harder! We're done here!
We're done here! We're done here!
Off my property! You have no right to be here!
We have every right to be here!
Dad, who's at the door?
I'll call my lawyer! Stop!
Min Min, go back to your room!
I'll be back to your room!
I'll be back to you!
Please, sir! Let me do my job!
This can't be completely unfounded!
Listen, it'd be easier if we could just talk to him, briefly.
Not a chance!
He's gone through more than enough already aside from this!
Don't make his life any harder!
We're done here! Off my property!
Who's at the door?
I'll call my lawyer!
Stop!
Min Min, go back to your room!
My son was paralyzed in a car accident!
How could he be out there hurting people?
Explain that to me!
If I follow through with this, I'm bound to get good intel!
Oh, I'm so sorry, Mr. Liu. I must have dozed off.
That's okay. You talked about your boss in your sleep. Sounds like a nightmare. Feel free to rest more if you like.
Oh, that's pretty embarrassing.
No worries. I shouldn't have mentioned it. So, you have big plans tonight?
Just heading home. With my parents. Then job hunting. It's silly. I used to dream of the city.
I wanted to live there. No matter what. But now that I think about it, another life might suit me better. A quieter one.
A quieter one.
Are we going the right way?
The GPS rerouted us. To avoid traffic.
Is that so? How long till we're there then?
You got me. We're not going to the station.
What do you mean?
Mr. Liu? What are you doing? Let me out. Here is fine. I'll walk home.
Is that so? Are you trying to run away with the money?
What are you...?
I know what your real name is. Wu Lihua, right?
But to make yourself seem more worldly, you gave yourself an English name, Emma.
You disgust me.
Emma? Why is she here?
You scheming idiots from the boonies are a plague. No matter how glamorously you repackage yourselves, it doesn't change who you are.
I didn't want to have to deal with your kind, but oh well.
Spit it out! Now! Where's my money?!
Please, please let me go. I'm sorry. I don't know what money you're talking about.
No.
Let me refresh your memory.
I don't understand. She was murdered?
Wait. Did he know?
Is it an interesting case?
I've looked at the photos. No luck. I'm sorry. We can't help.
He must have known that Emma was one of the victims.
That's why he didn't want us on the case.
Who's texting? It's late.
Better to not look.
This is... all because of me.
I'll kill you!
Darling, are you home yet?
Your father told me you got into some kind of trouble with your boss because I called earlier.
I'm so sorry.
Tell me you weren't stupid.
It's because...
of what I did.
Why can't parasites like you just leave me alone?
You live pathetic lives, then talk crap online so you can feel better!
You're jealous because you wish you had my money!
You'll pay! I promise! I'll kill every last one of you!
Every last one of you!
She isn't picking up.
We've been waiting for almost two hours. Where is she?
I hope nothing bad happened to her.
Why would you say something like that?
You shouldn't put thoughts like that into the universe.
I take it back.
I was just trying to be kind.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing. Just stick to the script, alright?
Listen, you know the rules. We go to the past, but we leave it like we found it.
Hey!
I was just trying to be kind.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing.
Just stick to the script, all right?
Listen, you know the rules.
We go to the past, but we leave it like we found it.
Hey.
Hey, don't question what's happened or the future will be altered.
Because of us.
Please guide me.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't get it.
It's like he just vanished.
Use your brain.
Please don't do anything stupid.
So, um, what's the deal?
Where did he go?
The thing is...
What? How? He just appeared out of nowhere.
Chao Ling?
Well, that's great. You'll let her see.
You don't get to be mad.
Why'd you go alone?
You could have died!
The things you did in the past warped the timeline,
and now everything's spinning out of control!
Why would you listen to me?
I know.
I understand now.
That's why I didn't try to help her.
What do you mean?
You know.
The girl who we spotted getting into the car...
was Emma.
Wait.
You mean the assistant at Trader Games?
She was one of the victims?
That's right.
And there's something else that you should know.
You've always blamed yourself about what happened to Dodo that day.
But it isn't your fault.
Because I'm the one to blame.
I distracted you.
Oh, let's check out the shop.
Maybe the line isn't too long yet.
Hey, it's you!
If I hadn't run into you during my dive...
you would've...
Wait, so...
you enter the photos?
That's right.
I go to the past and interact.
Liu watches me from the present.
He gives the instructions.
Is that the reason why the two of you wouldn't let me see you work this whole time?
You should've told me!
Hello, Officer Chun?
Did you catch him yet?
Did he say anything about my friend?
Well, we matched the license plate.
But it's no good.
He isn't our guy.
You're sure?
You saw one of the victims getting into that car, didn't you?
Emma from Trader Games.
It's clear the two of them are connected.
Figure it out.
How do you know all that?
Is someone leaking you info?
Here's the deal.
So?
Did they catch that bastard?
No.
Not yet.
Why not?
What are they doing?
Liumin couldn't have killed that woman.
We have the proof.
It'd be impossible, trust me.
That can't be!
Yeah.
Liumin was in the hospital whenever she died.
Plus, we found footage of her that night, walking alone on an old bridge.
I got lost in the street that I'm living in.
Or maybe I should just quit overthinking.
I used to have been thrown away.
I hear the îl meioय Jia in my neck.
I find out how long my eyes.
How did I get him?
You should not really stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it.
Stop stop thinking about it.
While your mind overclouded.
I'm videos of true jokingvolley.
I will want to do it like I'm on.
Stop thinking about it.
Stop thinking about it, stop stop thinking about it, why your mind overclouded?
In this time, I can't wait for a moment, but I understand how many worries are forever.
Stop thinking about it, stop thinking about it, stop stop thinking about it, why your mind overclouded?